[{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":4941,"timeElapsed":172174},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664222172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":7046,"timeElapsed":179224},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664231857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":9675,"timeElapsed":188908},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3201,"timeElapsed":192115},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664237066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1995,"timeElapsed":194118},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664239617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2545,"timeElapsed":196669},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664241060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":1435,"timeElapsed":198112},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664244176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3112,"timeElapsed":201228},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2274,"timeElapsed":203508},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4763,"timeElapsed":209376},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664253698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1370,"timeElapsed":210750},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4713,"timeElapsed":215470},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664261155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2734,"timeElapsed":218207},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664263965,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2806,"timeElapsed":221017},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664265442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1473,"timeElapsed":222494},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664267181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1736,"timeElapsed":224233},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664268908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1724,"timeElapsed":225960},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":923,"timeElapsed":226886},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664278312,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8469,"timeElapsed":235364},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664285975,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6649,"timeElapsed":243027},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664287263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1281,"timeElapsed":244315},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664288632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1364,"timeElapsed":245684},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664301999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":13364,"timeElapsed":259051},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664303770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1766,"timeElapsed":260822},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664305252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1475,"timeElapsed":262304},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1885,"timeElapsed":264193},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1634,"timeElapsed":265831},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664309573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"1","question":"Given the choice of anyone in the world (alive or dead), whom would you want as a dinner guest?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":792,"timeElapsed":266625},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664315374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4975,"timeElapsed":272426},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1049,"timeElapsed":273480},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664317414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":981,"timeElapsed":274466},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1083,"timeElapsed":275554},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664320040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1534,"timeElapsed":277092},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664321097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1052,"timeElapsed":278149},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664323326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2225,"timeElapsed":280378},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3048,"timeElapsed":283429},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664327605,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":1222,"timeElapsed":284656},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1151,"timeElapsed":286675},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":740,"timeElapsed":287421},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":705,"timeElapsed":288131},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":663,"timeElapsed":288798},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1356,"timeElapsed":290157},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":863,"timeElapsed":291023},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664335589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1615,"timeElapsed":292641},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":9461,"timeElapsed":302104},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":894,"timeElapsed":303003},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360556,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":13700,"timeElapsed":317608},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664361533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":971,"timeElapsed":318585},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664363601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2060,"timeElapsed":320653},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664364696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1088,"timeElapsed":321748},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1036,"timeElapsed":322792},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664367133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1385,"timeElapsed":324185},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1087,"timeElapsed":325278},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664369535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1303,"timeElapsed":326587},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"82","question":"What quality in people do you find most enviable?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":874,"timeElapsed":327471},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664374902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3548,"timeElapsed":331954},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664375878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":970,"timeElapsed":332930},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":871,"timeElapsed":333805},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664377614,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":856,"timeElapsed":334666},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378973,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1354,"timeElapsed":336025},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":891,"timeElapsed":336920},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664380794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":920,"timeElapsed":337845},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664381694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":895,"timeElapsed":338746},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":903,"timeElapsed":339655},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664390220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6633,"timeElapsed":347272},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664392317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":349369},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664393753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1432,"timeElapsed":350805},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664394704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":947,"timeElapsed":351756},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664396160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1453,"timeElapsed":353212},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664397576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1411,"timeElapsed":354628},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664399077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1496,"timeElapsed":356129},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664400501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1420,"timeElapsed":357553},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664401105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"152","question":"What was something fun or interesting you did over this past summer?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":601,"timeElapsed":358156},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664403921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2080,"timeElapsed":360973},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664404499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":573,"timeElapsed":361551},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664412192,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7690,"timeElapsed":369243},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664415987,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3791,"timeElapsed":373039},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664417793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1800,"timeElapsed":374845},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664419412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1617,"timeElapsed":376464},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664420849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1433,"timeElapsed":377901},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664422224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1371,"timeElapsed":379276},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664424279,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2052,"timeElapsed":381331},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"177","question":"How many times do you hit the snooze button in the morning?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1776,"timeElapsed":383111},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664433648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":6808,"timeElapsed":390699},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664434421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":772,"timeElapsed":391473},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":637,"timeElapsed":392114},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":611,"timeElapsed":392731},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664437413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1730,"timeElapsed":394465},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664438404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":986,"timeElapsed":395456},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664440529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":397581},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664441722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1190,"timeElapsed":398774},{"subjectID":"jofqrex31r","prolificID":"674ec67fc4434b39e440d90f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67742158d6aea0bb5d3ecd30","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":673,"timeElapsed":399452}]